Another one?
Coming
to see you.
right now
Takakura
Kanba
Shoma
Himari
Looks like no one's home.
留守みたい
困ったな　どうしよう
This sucks. What do we do now?
They're suspicious as hell!
怪しい　明らかに
Should we leave a note or something?
手紙とかおいてく　じゃここで書く
You want to write it here?
書くものある
Do you have something to write on?
ちょっと
Hey!
What business do you two creeps have here?
怪しい二人　この家に何の用
We're not creeps.
怪しい者ではありません
ただ　ちょっと
We just...
ひまりちゃんにお届け物です
have something for Himari.
少年少女輪になって
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
交わらないイマジナリー
majiwaranai imaginary
The Imaginary and the Real can never mingle
回転木馬宙を舞って
kaiten mokuba chuu wo matte
The merry-go-round twirls into the air
戦いの幕を切って落とす
tatakai no maku wo kitte otosu
As the curtain of war is torn open
秘め事明かすホーリーナイト
himegoto akasu holy night
The Holy Night for divulging secrets
真夜中開く窓
mayonaka hiraku mado temaneku nazo no koe
My window opens at night and a mysterious voice beckons
手招く謎の声
深紅のカーテンを翻して
shinku no curtain wo hirugaeshite hohoemi kakusu
A crimson curtain conceals the smile
微笑み隠す
少年よ我に帰れ
shounen yo ware ni kaere
Boys, come back to me
特急列車乗っちゃって
tokkyuu ressha nocchate
I ended up getting on the midnight express
ネバーランドに連れてって
neverland ni tsuretette
Take me away to Neverland
一切合切奪ってよ
issai gassai ubatte yo
Steal away everything I have
後ろ指さされたって
ushiro yubi sasaretatte
I don't care if you talk behind my back
一目散に逃げちゃっていいよ
ichimokusan ni nigechatte iiyo
I'll just run away at full speed
全部お気に召すまま
zenbu oki ni mesu mama
Do as you please
少年少女輪になって
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
回り始めるディステニー
mawari hajimeru destiny
Destiny begins to turn
本字幕由诸神字幕组（kamigami.org）制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于任何商业用途
日听：hunter 翻译:草泥马 校对:冷漠的风  木落 时间轴:wcaster 压制:wcaster
Double-H...
ダブルエッチ　本物だ
In the flesh!
私たち　ひまりちゃんに会いに来たんです
We came to see Himari.
ひまりちゃんとは小学校が同じで
We went to the same elementary school as Himari.
Himari knitted these for us.
これ　日まりちゃん編んでくれたんです
いつも 応援してるよ
"I'll always cheer you on."
"It's a symbol of our friendship," she said.
友情の絆だよって
That's why, we really wanted to see Himari in person and thank her for the scarves.
だから　どうしてもひまりちゃんに直接会って
マフラーのお礼が言いたくって
そうだったんだ
I see.
でも　ひまりちゃん出かけちゃって
But Himari's not home.
I don't think she'll be back today.
今日は帰って来ないと思う
そうですか
Oh...
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
それじゃ　これを　新曲なんです
Please pass this along to her.
It's our new song.
We want Himari to hear it.
ひまりちゃんに聞いてもらいたくて
Okay, I promise I'll get it to her.
うん　必ず渡すから
晶馬君
Shoma!
荻野目さん
Oginome.
さっきまた警察に行ってきた
I went to see the police again.
特に報告はないって
They said they didn't have any leads.
I see.
そう
ひまりちゃん　どうしておじさんの家に行かなかったのかな
I wonder why Himari didn't go to your uncle's place.
僕がバカだった　もっとひまりの気持を考えてやってれば
I was a fool.
I should've paid more attention to her feelings.
やっぱり　ひまりちゃん　冠葉君と一緒なんじゃないかな
I guess Himari is probably with Kanba.
いよいよ決行の時が来た
D-Day is finally here.
テディを一つの輪っかに50個投入しろ
Place 50 Teddies in each ring.
A Space Odyssey
ほかのルートの分は用意できたのか
Did you prepare for other routes?
Yes. Production is going smoothly.
はい　目下順調に作成中です
後三百必要だ
We need another 300.
間に合わせろよ
Make sure to meet the deadline.
Copy. I'm heading to the Forest.
了解　森へ行きます
了解　森へ行け
Copy. Head to the Forest.
まずいことになった
This is bad.
なんだ
What is it?
The dogs have sniffed out the Rolling Chamber.
ローリングの部屋が犬に嗅ぎつけられたらしい
あそこには計画の一部を記したデータが残されている
Some of our mission data is still in there.
We must delete it.
それをデリートしなくては
よし その森には俺が行く
Okay.
I will head to that Forest.
もうあの薬が効かないんだ
That medicine won't work anymore.
Kanba - That Night - To'oh Hospital examination room - Unbelievable words from Sanetoshi. I just want to save Himari.
ふざけんな　　どういうことだよ
Stop messing with me!
What do you mean by that?
Medicine loses its potency if you keep using it.
薬っていうのは使い続けると効かなくなるんだよ
そういう話　聞いたことあるだろう
Haven't you heard that before?
じゃ　ひまりは
Then, Himari is...
Going to die.
死ぬね
貴様　殺してやる
Why you little...
I'll kill you!
無駄だよ
It's no use.
君にはボクを殺さないよ
You can't kill me.
でも　大丈夫
But don't worry.
There is still one way to save your sister.
まだ　一つだけ妹を救える方法があるんだ
Just abide by our curse like a good boy.
君が僕たちの呪いに素直に従えばいいのさ
冠ちゃん
Kan.
どうした
What is it?
うーん　ちょっとだけ
Nothing. Just let me be.
ずっと一緒だからね　冠ちゃん
We'll always be together, Kan.
大好きだよ
I love you.
I finally realized...
私ね　分かったの　もう怖がらなくていいんだって
that I don't have to be afraid anymore.
冠ちゃんが教えてくれたんだよ
You taught me that.
ありがとう
Thank you.
だから　もう十分
So...
You've done enough.
ごめんね　今まで苦しかったでしょう
I'm sorry for everything. It must have been tough.
俺が選んだことだ
I've chosen this path on my own.
No.
うーん　私見て見ぬ振りをしてた
I've been turning a blind eye to the fact...
Kokoro
私のために　冠ちゃんがすべてを犠牲にしてたことを
That you sacrificed everything for me...
Even putting your life on the line.
命までかけて
覚えてるか　ひまり
Do you remember, Himari?
俺たちが家族になった日の事を
The day we became family.
覚えてるよ
I remember.
お前があの時　俺に与えてくれた物を
What you gave me back then...
与えた　私が冠ちゃんに
What I... gave you?
Never mind.
いや　いいんだ
俺は必ずお前を助ける
I will definitely save you.
やめて
Don't!
やめて　冠ちゃん
Don't... Kan.
恐ろしいことはしないで
Don't do anything terrible.
私　もう死んでもいいから
I don't mind if I die.
No.
いや　お前が死んだら　俺はこの世界を許さない
I won't forgive this world if you die.
この世界を焼き尽くす
I will burn this world to ash!
行ってくる
I'm off.
ひまり　お前は俺のすべてなんだ
Himari, you are the world to me.
待って
Wait!
待って　冠ちゃん
Wait, Kan!
ママ　すごい
Wow Mom!
みてみて　ペンギン泳ぐの上手だね
Look! Penguins are such good swimmers!
上手ね
They sure are.
ここは
This is...
そうだ　あの日　あの時
Yes.
On that day, on that very moment...
私があのまま死んでさえいれば
If only I'd stayed dead then...
そしたら　冠ちゃんは
Then Kan wouldn't...
神様　お願いです
God, I beg of you.
私が見て見ぬふりをして
Return everything that was taken from him as I turned a blind eye, back to Kan.
冠ちゃんから奪った物を　冠ちゃんに返してあげてください
どうか　冠ちゃんを助けてあげて
Please, save Kan.
私が冠ちゃんからもらったすべてを
I hereby return everything Kan has given me... my life.
命を返しますから
I'm sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
ごめんなさいね　急に呼び出したりして
いいえ　でも何があったんですか
I don't mind, but...
What happened?
Yuri - Ramen Shop -- Inside - The night revenge ended - The blade pointed at me. It was an unexpected person who tried to stab me. Who would've thought it'd turn out...
危ない
Watch out!
多蕗君
Tabuki!
I-It's not my fault.
ぼ　僕のせいじゃない
全部　全部君が悪いんだ
You're to blame for everything!
君は恋と罪のバロックなんだ
You're a baroque of love and sin!
I'm calling an ambulance!
今　救急車を
Yuri...
ゆり　やっと分かったよ
I finally figured out.
Yuri, I finally figure out.
何が
What is it?
どうして僕たちだけがこの世界に残されたかが
I figured out why we were left behind in this world.
教えて
Tell me.
君と僕は予め失われた子供だった
You and I were already beyond help as children.
でも　世界中のほとんどの子供たちは僕たちと同じだよ
But most children in the world are just like us us.
So, just once was enough...
だから　たった一度でもよかった
誰かの愛しているっていう言葉が 僕たちには必要だったんだ
We just needed someone to tell us that we were loved.
The police have already caught wind of your mission.
あなたたちの計画はもう警察に気づかれている
They've got their eyes on you, even at this very moment.
今　この時も彼らはあなたを見張っているの
Now's the time to pull out.
手を引くなら　今しかないわ
I will accomplish the mission no matter what and save Himari's life.
俺は必ず計画を成し遂げて
ひまりの命を救う
Watch out.
気をつけろ
Their undercover vehicles are tailing us in rotation.
やつらが覆面車両がロータリーでわれわれを張っている
Okay, leave it to me.
よし　任せろ
What...
何を　するつもり
are you up to?
Someone, call the police!
誰か警察呼んで
What's going on?
なんだよ　今のは
ママ　怖いよ
It's dangerous!
おい　危ねぇよ
He just came out.
出てきたぞ
Hurry, run!
早く逃げなさい
What just happened?
何が起こったろう
爆発したぜ
How could you...
なんてことを
Stop this!
やめなさい　あなたは彼らに利用されてるのよ
They're using you!
And it's not just that!
いえ　それだけじゃない
I figured out that man's identity!
あの男の正体が分かったのよ
He's a curse.
あれは呪いなの　あの男はこの世のものじゃ
He's not from this worl-
Wait!
待て
We have you surrounded.
君は包囲されている
Resistance is futile, surrender now.
無駄な抵抗をやめて
投降しなさい
I repeat.
繰り返す
We have you surrounded.
君は包囲されている
Resistance is futile, surrender now.
無駄な抵抗をやめて
投降しなさい
Kanba, let's surrender.
冠葉　投降しましょう
I will go with you.
わたくしも一緒に行くから　大丈夫
Everything will be okay.
You head home now.
お前はここで帰れ
Don't follow me.
ついてくるな
What's this place?
ここは
The city's underground is a labyrinth.
この街の地下は迷路だ
No one has stepped into many of its uncharted territories for tens of years.
どこにも記録されず
もう何十年も人が足を踏み入れてない空間がたくさんある
We are using one of them.
その一つを　俺たちは使っている
No one will ever find it.
絶対に誰にも見つけられない
Are you serious about this?
本気なの
It's to save Himari's life.
ひまりの命を救うためだ
Why?
どうしてなの
She's a mere stranger!
あの子は赤の他人じゃない
Himari is my little sister.
ひまりは俺の妹だ
Look at me.
わたくしを見て　あなたの妹はわたくしよ
I'm your little sister.
Open your eyes!
目を覚まして　わたくしたちは過去に呪われているのよ
We were cursed in the past.
You understand very well what a terrible thing our father had done.
わたくしたちの父親がどれほど恐ろしいことをしたか
あなただって　分かっているでしょう
He was used up and then tossed away.
そして父を　あの人たちに使い捨てられた
Stop following me.
もう　ついてくるな
No, I won't let you go.
駄目　行かさない
I've been fighting ever since that day.
あの日から　わたくしはずっと戦ってきたの
So that no one else would be stolen from me.
これ以上　奪われないために
So that I wouldn't lose anything else.
失わないために
If you go now, they'll use you up for sure...
今行けば　あなたもきっと使い捨てられる
They'll kill you for sure.
きっと殺されてしまう
Shut up.
黙れ
No!
いや　わたくしは二度 あなたを失いたくない
I don't want to lose you again!
Please...
お願い　言って
Tell me...
That I'm your precious little sister.
わたくしはあなたの大切な妹だと
Tell me just once more, like you did in the past.
一度だけ　昔みたいに言って
Then I wouldn't mind being cursed with you for all eternity.
そうしたら　わたくし
あなたと一緒に未来永劫呪われてもいいから
Masako...
真砂子
There's no escape now.
もう逃げられない　諦めて投降しなさい
Give up and surrender.
We have you completely surrounded.
君は完全に包囲されている
Resistance is futile, surrender now.
無駄な抵抗はやめて　投降しなさい
Damn it.
クソ
I repeat.
もう一度繰り返す
We have you completely surrounded.
君は完全に包囲されている
Resistance is futile, surrender now.
無駄な抵抗はやめて　投降しなさい
There's no escape now.
もう逃げられない
The pests are gone now.
これでうるさいのはいなくなったな
Kanba?
冠葉
You've already...
あなた　もう
Masako!
真砂子
No...
駄目
Brother...
お兄様
Never let me go.
真砂子を　放さないで
Masako - 10 Years Ago - Condo - The day I parted with Kanba. My brother abandoned the Natsume clan to keep everything for Mario and me...
I will keep Masako and Mario by my side!
真砂子とマリオは私の側に置く
I will have them stay with me here!
ここにずっといてもらう
Father, I will stay behind.
父さん　俺がここに残るよ
So please, return Masako and Mario to the Natsume clan.
だから　真砂子とマリオは
夏芽の家に帰してあげて
Let them lead normal lives.
普通の子にしてあげて
No! Brother!
駄目　お兄様
Never let me go!
真砂子を離さないで
Kanba...
冠葉　冠葉
Kanba!
There's no escape now, Kanba Takakura.
もう逃げられないぞ　高倉冠葉君
Resistance is futile.
無駄な抵抗はやめなさい
I repeat.
繰り返す
There's no escape now, Kanba Takakura.
もう逃げられないぞ　高倉冠葉君
Resistance is futile.
無駄な抵抗はやめなさい
まずいな　包囲されている
This is bad.
We're surrounded.
What do we do?
どうする
They'll get us at this rate.
このままではやられる　しかし
But...
Please, surrender!
お願い　投降して
It's no use.
無駄だ　彼らは決してわれわれを許さない
They will never forgive us.
If we go out now, they'll kill us.
出ていけば　殺されるだろう
How can that be?
そんな
We will give you 30 seconds.
三十秒を待つ　それまでに投降しなさい
Surrender before then.
Mario...
マリオさん　ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
I couldn't save you.
あなたを救えなかった
Very well.
いいわ　わたくしが囮になる
I will be the bait.
While I buy you time, Kanba...
その間に　冠葉を
The curse of the Natsume clan.
夏芽家の呪い　祖父の呪い
The curse of my grandfather.
This world only bears fruit for the greedy.
この世界は強欲なものだけにしか
実りの果実を与えようとしない
So, I thought my father, who had thrown away everything, was a beautiful person.
だから　すべて見捨てた父をわたくしは美しい人だと思っていた
But, beauty that can be seen must also come with a shadow.
でも　目に見える美しさには　必ず影がある
That place was a beautiful casket.
あそこは美しい棺
I was a child who failed to notice.
わたくしはそのことに気づかない子供だった
Kanba.
冠葉　あなたは　わたくしとマリオさんを
You saved Mario and me from that shadow.
その影から救い出してくれた
To the world lit by the sun.
日の当たる世界へ
It's my turn now.
今度はわたくしの番　あなたをこんな闇の中で死なせはしない
I will not let you die in this darkness!
Gosh, I must crush them soon.
いやだわ　早くすり潰さないと
The Beautiful Casket
ashita no kageri no naka de omae wo omou
I think about you in shadows of tomorrow
mitsumeteru yogoreta chizu wo hitori no heya de
I'm looking at the the worn-out map alone in the room
radio no koe wa amaku hito wo yowaseteru
All the listeners are drown in the sweet voice from the radio
hakushu no uzu no naka mata kurikaesu no sa
It all repeats amidst the waves of applause
orokana game wo aitsu no aizu de
On his cue, we move forward
oretachi wa chess no coma no you ni susumerare
Like chess pieces in this stupid game
orokana game no tsuzuki ga hajimaru
We're about to continue moving forward
oretachi wa chess no coma no you ni susumerare
Like chess pieces in this stupid game
kesareteku
Being deleted
Shoma - Inside the Box - 10 years ago - I was all alone. I have no idea what happened. Why am I here...
Where am I?
ここは　どこ
Why am I here?
どうして 僕はこんなところにいるんだ
We've lost everything.
僕たちはすべてを失った
Are you still going to continue?
それでもお前は続けるのか
It's unforgivable.
許さないぞ　決着をつけよう
Let's settle this once and for all.
Lily Hoshino
Survival Strategy. Never let me go.
生存戦略　私を放さないで